So we've kind of finished with the first half
我们已经完成了这一系列的
of the series.
差不多前一半了
Now we're going to move on and we're going to change the format up
现在我们继续，不过我们要改一下我们的学习方式
just a little bit.
仅仅是一点而已
Up to this point we would cover some topics
到了这一步，我们将要探讨一些
that were loosely related,
之前较少提及的话题
then we would have a cheat sheet session,
之后我们还会有个整理笔记的部分
then I would assign a challenge,
接着我还会发布一个挑战任务
in order to reinforce those ideas.
用来巩固这些概念
Now we're going to kind of move past that,
现在，我们先不说这些
move on to a new format where we're going to build
这次换到新的方式，我们将从零开始，创建
four entire applications from scratch.
四个完整的应用
So a lot of times the developers that I've spoken to
很长时间以来，我遇到许多的开发者
through the years, they understand C#
他们懂得C#语言
they understand Object-Oriented Programming.
他们理解面向对象编程，
But they don't understand how to decompose something
但是他们不懂得如何把他们脑海里面的想法分解
in their head and make a full application out of it.
并从中构建一个完整的应用程序
So hopefully this process will illustrate how to do that.
因此希望本次过程能够诠释是如何做到这一点
Secondly we're going to move into other areas
其次，我们还将涉及UWP中
of the Universal Windows Platform
一些我们还没有提及过的
that we haven't talked about yet.
其他领域的内容
Learn some new techniques,
去学习一些新的技巧
some new features of Visual Studio.
和一些Visual Studio新的特性
So there'll be a lot to learn taking this other tact
我们学习构建应用的过程中，将会
as we approach this material.
学到的许多其他的技巧
So feel free to follow along, that would be great.
我们继续吧，接下来会非常有趣
I'm going to move fast, I'll warn you right up front.
这次我将要快一点，但在事先我可要提醒你
Make sure that you reference the snapshots
一定要配合每个视频附件里的工程文件
for each video.
进行学习
So at the end of each video I'd copy off
在每一个视频的结尾，我将会打包
the current state of the code into its own .zip file.
包含了当前代码状态的 .zip 压缩文件
So make sure you download that .zip file
因此确保你下载了压缩文件
and you take a look at the code that I typed in there.
并且看一眼我放在里面的代码
Or you're going to be pausing or rewinding a lot,
你看视频的时候可能会经常暂停或者回放
which is fine too.
那也是极好的
But you might find more satisfaction at looking at
但你也许会发现看着我手打的代码，
that actual code that I typed in.
感觉会更爽一点
So what are we going to learn?
So..我们到底要学什么
Well let's go ahead and run the application
好，先跑一下应用
and first of all I wanted to point out that you see that
首先，我想说明一下你看到的
red splash screen.
红色的载入界面
We'll talk about that.
我们将要聊一聊
How we were able to achieve that
我们是如何来实现它的
by modifying the Package.appxmanifest file.
通过修改Package.appxmanifest文件
And that will be near the end of our development effort
然后它会接近在这个应用中开发
on this application.
的最终效果
But we can add resources that'll be utilized in the store,
我们还可以添加一些可能在商店中使用的资源
on the start bar, and the splash page, things like that.
一些像是在开始栏、 载入界面中需要使用的
Alright so you can see that I had
好，你现在可以看到在我
this simple soundboard application.
屏幕上面的这个简单的声音板应用
The idea here is that there is an icon for each sound.
这想法就是每一个图标对应一个声音
I've only included a handful of sounds.
我仅仅包含了有限个声音素材
Feel free to flush this out, add as many sounds
你可以随意修改，添加更多的声音
and more functionality if you want.
也可以添加更多的功能
But the idea here is that you can find a category
但是这里你可以发现一个小创意，它使用了
of sounds using the hamburger navigation.
汉堡导航的声音分类目录
And then we find one that you want to play,
当你发现一个你想播放的图案
you just tap on it,(sound effect)
你就放上去 (duang~)
click on it and it will play that sound.
然后按一下，它就会播放声音
Okay so clearly hamburger navigation,
显然地，汉堡导航使用了
using the back buttons, State Management,
回退按钮，状态管理
looking at the AutoSuggestBox we are able
看看这个自动提示框，我们能
to find one specific sound,
搜到一个特定的声音
play that,(cow mooing)
然后播放（牟  牟~）
and then clear out that sound and have
然后清空这声音
the state of the application return back to normal.
将应用的状态退回到正常状态
There's also clearly we're using media here
这里很显然地，我们使用了媒体文件
we're using sound so we're going to demonstrate
我们使用了声音，因此我们将演示一下
the use of the Media element,
如何使用Media element这个组件
which allows you to play video and sounds
它可以让你播放视频和音频
and various functionality around that new User Control.
围绕新的用户控制，做到多样的功能
We're also going to demonstrate drag-and-drop
我将演示一下拖放的功能
so here's a .mp3 file that i have on my desktop
在我们的桌面上有一个mp3文件
and I was going to drag it and drop it.
我将拖动它然后放进去
Alright and this is a little song
好的，这是一首音乐
that was played by a friend.
它是一个朋友演奏的
It's actually kinda long so,(sound effect)
它实际有点长
if you play another sound it will cancel that one out.
如果你播放另一个声音就可以取消它
That was purely accidental but a cool feature none the less.
这单纯的是个意外，但依然是个很酷的功能
Okay we've already talking about
好，我们已经讨论了
the Package.appxmanifest.
关于Package.appxmanifest 这个文件
And then finally what we're going to do
然后我们最后要做的
after we build this application,
在我们构建好这个应用之后
is we're going to submit it to the store,
就是将这个应用发布到商店里面
walk through that entire process
走完一整套的流程
and then just to kind of restate this,
这里还要重新声明一下
I've already built this application.
我已经做好了这个应用
I'm coming back to record this video
我是在我完成这个应用之后，回头
after I've finished.
录制了这个视频
And at the very end,
在这之后
I left you with a cliffhanger.
我还留了一个非常厉害的挑战
You know, is this actually going to pass?
那个视频真的会被通过吗？
Am I going to be able to get this thing into the Window Store?
我真的能把这玩意发布到windows商店里面？
And so just this morning I got this notification
但就是今早，我收到了通知
that your submission for UWP SoundBoard passed certification
这个UWP SoundBoard的应用通过了审核
Alright, so it's in the store
好吧，事实它已经在商店里面了
it will be published within 24 hours.
它将会在24小时内被发布
Alright so that's pretty cool.
好吧，这真TM牛逼
So it actually worked.
它已经没问题了
So the cliffhanger I leave you at the end
我在最后视频中留给你们的
of the last video with,
精彩刺激的挑战
I've already, it's going to be anti-climactic
我已经完成了，它可能就不再是那么刺激了
because you already know that it will pass.
因为你已经知道它最终会被通过
And I didn't do anything off-camera.
我没有离开摄像头做任何事
Everything you saw was what I did here on camera.
你看到的一切都是我在摄像头之前做的
Alright so hopefully this will be
好滴，希望它对你来说将会是
a great learning exercise for you.
一段绝妙的学习实践
Again, different format, so don't let that throw you.
还要强调，不同的学习方式，不要它缠住你
Please follow along, if not by writing code
请跟上节奏，如果你不是在写代码
at least stay engaged as I write it.
当我写代码时，至少保持专注
It'll be a little bit dryer
这将会有一点点的枯燥
because I'll be talking to myself a lot
因为更多的是我在自言自语，
instead of talking to you.
而不是同你们讲的
But hopefully you'll get some value out of it.
但是希望你们有所收获
Okay, let's start up in the next lesson.
好的，让我们从下一节课开始
Thanks.
微软大法好